123exp-biographies.com 2009-06-16

# Privacy Policy - 123explore!

We respect your privacy. We have developed and provided this Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices and policies regarding the collection, use, maintenance, and disclosure of any information we obtain from you. We are providing you with this information so you can make an informed decision whether to visit our web site and whether you wish to voluntarily provide any personal information. Our Privacy Policy is described in the following sections. 

**COOKIES**

"Cookies" are small data files that are written to and stored on your hard drive when you visit a web site. They do not read files on your hard drive. Like most web sites, we use cookies to personalize a user's experience of our web site and to make it easier for users to complete forms. Our cookies do not track user movement once you leave our web site, except for noting your destination address.

Most web browsers allow the user to be notified upon the proposed installation of a cookie and the user can then decline the cookie. Even if you decline the cookie, you may continue to use our entire web site.

We use information received from our cookies for marketing purposes and to improve our on-line offering of services and products. We may also do so to evaluate our site's technical capacity and to review the navigational structure of our site, e.g., to revise or restructure our web site for easier and more intuitive movement throughout.

Currently, the information we collect with cookies is only reviewed in an aggregated form, which is not personally identifiable. In the future, however, we may correlate the information received from cookies with personally identifiable information, to identify specific users and track their web site usage. This personally identifiable information will be limited to contact information, such as the user's name, address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address. Our use of this combined information will continue to be solely for the purposes stated above with respect to information collected through cookies.

Whether or not the information received from cookies is correlated to any specific user, we do not disclose, sell, rent or share any information derived from cookies with any third parties.

**LOG FILES**

We review information contained in log files located on our web server, which record the date and time of each visit to our web site, the user's IP (internet protocol) address, the referring IP address or domain (the prior web site visited), and the files viewed on our web site (including HTML pages, graphics, etc.). We use log file information to analyze data in the aggregate to determine the trends and usage of our site. We can not correlate the log data to identify specific users. We do not disclose, sell, rent or share any information derived from log files with any third parties.

**VOLUNTARILY PROVIDED INFORMATION**

If you register for or enroll in a program or service through our web site, respond to a request for information or make any other on-line request of us, you will be voluntarily providing personally identifiable information. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, we ask that you please do not provide the requested information. You may nevertheless continue to use most of our web site, subject, however, to the collection of information through log files as discussed above. If you have previously provided personally identifiable information by registration through our web site, you may request to be removed from our active database of mailing lists. Voluntarily provided information is used to send you announcements of new products, updates, and promotional information, as well as to provide the services or goods that you request and give you better customer service. We share do not share personally identifiable information with anyone. 

**LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY WEB SITES**

Through our web pages, you may connect to third parties' web sites via hyperlinks, and the connections may or may not be obvious. We are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of information by such third parties. We encourage our users to be aware of the varied privacy policies of web sites that they visit.

**THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING COMPANIES**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**CORRESPONDENCE**

We maintain and review e-mail correspondence that you send to us. We will use (and maintain in a file specific to you) the personally identifiable information disclosed in the e-mail. Because such correspondence contains information that is not transmitted through the operation of our web site, it is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**REQUIRED DISCLOSURES OF INFORMATION**

Regardless of anything in this Privacy Policy to the contrary, we may disclose personally identifiable information, with or without prior notice to you, when we believe that the law requires it, in response to subpoenas or at the demand of governmental agencies, to protect our systems or business, to protect other visitors to the web site, or to respond to an emergency. If you partake, or we reasonably suspect you of partaking in any illegal activity we may also disclose your personally identifiable information, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order. We may also make disclosures of your personally identifiable information with your affirmative consent.

**MAINTENANCE AND TRANSMISSION OF INFORMATION**

Although we use reasonable efforts to maintain the privacy of your personally identifiable information, due to technological limitations, and the risk of unlawful interceptions and accessing of transmissions and/or data, we cannot completely assure you, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information, and any other electronically communicated information, will be absolutely confidential. For all e-commerce transactions, we use industry-standard commercial encryption technology to protect the information that you transmit to us via our web site. Although this technology is not flawless, we believe that it provides reasonable protection for your information. We will endeavor to update our protective devices as encryption technology develops further. Once received, personally identifiable information is protected by "firewalls," and access within our company is generally limited to the sales, marketing, and information technology departments. 

**USERS UNDER 13**

This web site is not directed at children under the age of 13. If you are younger than 13, please do not provide any personally identifiable information in connection with your use of the web site.

**ASSIGNMENT**

We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from our visitors to a third party in the event that we sell or transfer substantially all of our assets related to the web site to such third party.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Due to changing technological and marketing demands, we must reserve the right to change our policies regarding the privacy of your personally identifiable information in the future. If that happens, we will endeavor to promptly update this Privacy Policy. We may also attempt to provide a message to our customers whose e-mail addresses we have, in conformity with this Privacy Policy, advising of any such change(s). Your continued use of the web site following changes to this policy will indicate that you accept the changes.
